citizensbanking.com 2007-12-25

# Citizens Bank: Privacy Statement

## Citizens Republic Bancorp affiliates:

  * Citizens Bank Wealth Management, N.A.
  * Citizens Bank
  * Citizens Bank Mortgage Company, LLC
  * F&M Bank-Iowa
  * F&M Insurance Services

### We use client information in the ordinary course of serving your relationship or managing your business.

For example, we use your information to:

  * Identify you and protect you from fraud, so that others cannot use your accounts without your authorization.
  * Process your requests, such as, wire transfers, ATM withdrawals or loan applications.
  * Inform you of additional financial services to meet your individual needs.
  * Service your accounts, by issuing your account statements, checks and ATM cards.

### We collect information in the course of providing financial services to you.

In the process of serving your financial needs, we collect “nonpublic personal information,” which is information we receive about you in the course of providing financial services to you. This information helps us better serve your accounts and understand your needs, and may come from a variety of sources, including:

  * Information we receive directly from you, on applications and other forms, such as your name, address and assets.
  * Information we receive through your transactions or experiences with us, such as your account balance, overdraft history, or parties to transactions.
  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies and others as we set up your client relationship, including credit reports, property appraisals, or verification of employment.

### Information is shared only as required to service your accounts and help you achieve your financial goals.

We are very restrictive with your personal information. There are two primary reasons for the information we collect:

  * To provide you with greater convenience. For example, to allow you to use ATMs owned by other banks, or to allow us to serve you by telephone.
  * To help you meet your financial goals, by informing you of additional financial services that may be of interest or value to you.

### Citizens Republic Bancorp affiliates use information to work together to meet your financial needs.

Affiliates are financial service companies that are part of the Citizens Republic Bancorp family through common ownership or control, and are listed at the beginning of this statement. Our affiliates share nonpublic personal information internally among ourselves so that we can serve you more efficiently, offer you new services such as mortgages, insurance and investments, and reduce the amount of information you need to furnish every time you deal with us.

We are permitted by law to share with our affiliates information about your transactions or experiences with us. For example, we are permitted to share information about your account history, account balance and payment history. We do not share any other information such as income or credit history with our affiliates.

### We provide information to select outside companies in order to service your accounts or help us introduce new services to you.

We share nonpublic personal information, as described above, with nonaffiliated third parties who provide support services for us such as contract programming or check printing services, as well as selected financial services companies who provide special offers to our clients under joint marketing agreements with us.

This enables us to provide quality service to you and offer you additional financial services that may be of value to you. These arrangements are subject to strict standards of confidentiality and security. The information we provide is limited to that which we reasonably believe they “need to know” to provide their contracted services.

In addition, we may disclose your nonpublic personal information, as described above, to third parties as permitted by law. For example, we might be required to disclose information about you in response to a subpoena or to a credit bureau or under certain federal or state laws. Or we may provide information to others with your consent, for example, to complete a transaction that you have initiated.

### We vigilantly protect the security and confidentiality of client information.

We have implemented procedures and guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your nonpublic personal information from unauthorized use or improper access. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technologies become available. In addition, we restrict access to information about you to those staff members who have a business need to know that information in order to provide financial services to you. Our staff members are governed by a code of conduct and are educated about our privacy policies, and about the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of client information.

### At Citizens we take a number of additional steps to protect the privacy of your information:

  * We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. Should you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information, please notify us by calling 1-800-806-1692 or visiting your banking office. We will investigate your concerns and correct any inaccuracies.
  * If medical information is collected in the course of providing insurance services to you, please be assured that this information will not be used for any purpose other than which you originally requested.
  * Our strict policies for protecting nonpublic personal information apply to current clients as well as inactive or former clients. “Clients” refers to individuals who apply for, or use the products and services provided through the affiliates listed in this notification, or have done so in the past, for personal, family, or household purposes.

### Once again, we value your relationship, and will continue to protect your privacy and keep your client information secure. Thank you for the opportunity to serve you.

This policy is designed to comply with the privacy provisions in Title V of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, including applicable federal privacy regulations issued as part of that Act. It incorporates the policies of the affiliates of Citizens Republic Bancorp listed at the beginning of this document. Citizens reserves the right to revise this policy as necessary.

In addition, as we establish new affiliates in the future, these privacy standards will apply as well.

Citizens Republic Bancorp © 2007 GLB
